{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/51622852","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622852","name":"Asian Corned Beef","address":"3741 E. Seven Mile","zipcode":"48234","owner":"","licenseNumber":"230563","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"150","coords":"-83.06627,42.43323","geojson":{"id":"51622852","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.06626924,42.433232859]},"properties":{"name":"Asian Corned Beef","owner":"","address":"3741 E. Seven Mile","zipcode":"48234","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"230563","establishmentid":"51622852","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"150","most_recent_license_date":null}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"1557","name":"Dairy Queen","address":"3741 Seven Mile Rd. E.","zipcode":"48238"},{"establishmentid":"5128","name":"Yonka Grill & Dairy","address":"3741 Seven Mile E.","zipcode":"48234"},{"establishmentid":"4391","name":"Xtreme Ice Cream","address":"3741 Seven Mile Rd E. ","zipcode":"48203"},{"establishmentid":"888","name":"Pershing Senior High","address":"18875 Ryan Rd.","zipcode":"48234"},{"establishmentid":"4552","name":"Club Liquid","address":"3543 Seven Mile Rd. E.","zipcode":"48234"},{"establishmentid":"1893","name":"Club Liquid","address":"3537 Seven Mile Rd. E.","zipcode":"48234"},{"establishmentid":"3303","name":"Mamma's Coney Island","address":"3303 Seven Mile Rd. E.","zipcode":"48234"},{"establishmentid":"1255","name":"Vernon Chapel Church","address":"18500 Norwood","zipcode":"48234"},{"establishmentid":"1751","name":"Ambiance","address":"2959 Seven Mile Rd. E.","zipcode":"48234"},{"establishmentid":"733","name":"Gold Coast","address":"2971 Seven Mile Rd. E.","zipcode":"48234"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"52282","inspectionDate":"2020-04-02T00:00:00","inspectionType":"COVID19-temp closed","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"50723","inspectionDate":"2020-02-03T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Hot food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored below 135 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"MICROWAVE","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"TABLE","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"47951","inspectionDate":"2019-05-30T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"EQUIPMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-202.16","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall be free of unnecessary ledges, projections, and crevices, and designed and constructed to allow easy cleaning and to facilitate maintenance.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"MICROWAVE","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-501.113","violationDescription":"Receptacles and waste handling units for REFUSE, recyclables, and returnables shall be kept tightly covered, unless they are in continuous use.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Waste container(s)/container(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not covered","subProblem":"","location":"OUTSIDE PREMISES","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-204.11","violationDescription":"Exhaust ventilation hood systems in FOOD preparation and WAREWASHING areas including components such as hoods, fans, guards, and ducting shall be designed to prevent grease or condensation from draining or dripping onto FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Exhaust ventilation hood system(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Designed to allow grease or condensation from draining/dripping onto","subProblem":"","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"44724","inspectionDate":"2018-12-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for culinary purposes","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2012-01-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discontinue use of hand sink for this use and use appropriate sink."},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2012-01-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-13T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622852"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}